(Leonard:)Yeah, thanks,
but nobody asked you.
(Theodore:)Well, I'm just gonna
keep on talking.
(Theodore:)Seems like, with Sheldon
(Theodore:)moving out, you're
in a new phase of your lives
(Theodore:)and it's easier
(Theodore:)to fight than
to face the feelings
(Theodore:)that you have for one another.
(Amy:)I think he might be right.
(Amy:)Also, who is that?
(Sheldon:)I have to admit,
(Sheldon:)leaving you to
move in with Amy
(Sheldon:)has been harder than
I thought it would be.
(Leonard:)Well, for me, too.
(Leonard:)It's not the same
with you gone.
(Theodore:)If you're looking for a new guy
to live with...
-No!
- We're good. Thank you.
(Amy:)So, no one's gonna
tell me? Okay.
(Sheldon:)Leonard,
(Sheldon:)I would like us
to stop fighting
(Sheldon:)about our possessions.
(Leonard:)Well, I'd like that, too.
(Sheldon:)In fact, I want you to
keep the apartment flag,
(Sheldon:)and I'm not
just saying that
(Sheldon:)because it touched
your genitals.